They brought the kid here just recently.
And based on our records, he's now an orphan.
Do you know the kid's parents?
I thought he was here
because he got separated from his parents.
It turns out he's an orphan.
You can remove me from this project,
but retain Joyce.
Joyce will stay in the project
if you return to Casa Fuerte.
Liam is not working at Blacksmith anymore.
He's going back to Casa Fuerte.
You resigned at Blacksmith?
What about our movie?
I don't have a choice, Joyce.
If there's something I learned
in making our film,
that is we all have a choice.
You taught me how to be brave.
But I went overboard. I did Via wrong.
Don't blame yourself.
I have no one else to blame but myself.
And I think you should also do that.
Take full accountability
for all of your decisions.
Are you having an affair with my boyfriend?
Nothing's going on between me and Liam.
He called me Joyce.
I didn't know who Joyce was.
Until I found out that you are Joyce.
Could it be Sir Liam?
I hope so.
How's everyone doing?
Here's the script from Liam...
His final input for the film.
What's taking him so long?
Liam doesn't get late, my friend.
I'm sure he's on his way.
We can now start!
Our creative manager is here.
What are you doing here?
Does Dad know you're here?
I will finish what I started.
You really have gone crazy.
Liam, you are going against
Congressman Ramon.
VLH, let's talk about that later.
I'm busy.
The set is ready, Sir Liam.
Sir Liam, let's start filming.
Vergil.
Okay, thank you.
Liam is at the shooting.
Your son is messing with me!
Go on!
Chito... Chito!
Chito?
Chito!
Chito, hold on. Wake up.
Wake up. We'll go home together.
We'll go home to our town.
Chito...
Chito... Chito, wait...
I love you so much.
Chito, I love you so much.
Chito!
Sir Liam, why did you kill the hero?
They're still filming.
Chito!
Cut!
Good take.
Lovely!
- Perfect.
- Wow.
PA, please assist the actors. Hurry!
Makeup, tissue!
Good job, guys.
Good job.
Odet, water, please.
Okay.
Great.
Show them the fight scene. How is it done?
Don't!
- Why?
- I'm better than you, Sir Liam.
My mom told me to eat my vegetables.
And I'm an obedient boy.
So what?
You can make me eat anything except for that.
Eat it!
I don't want that.
- Go and eat that.
- You eat it.
No. You eat first.
You eat it.
Ouch!
Sorry!
Sorry. It's your fault. You're so stubborn.
I said eat this.
- I said no.
- What's happening here?
Sir Liam doesn't want to eat okra.
You don't eat okra?
I can't eat it.
Have you eaten yet? Finish your food.
I eat okra.
- Let me see if you really eat okra.
- Sit here.
You're forcing Liam to eat it.
- Eat up.
- Eat this first.
Show us that you eat it.
- He's not eating it.
- Let's see if you eat vegetables.
Ready?
- I don't want it!
- Eat it.
- Eat it!
- Don't spit it out.
Eat it.
Go on.
It's good, right?
It's good, isn't it?
Gosh.
Do you really have to be fed
before you eat it?
How about you?
Gosh.
One more, one more.
No! I don't want it anymore.
One is enough.
Here you go, Sep. Eat your food.
What's gotten into you?
Why did you come back?
Okra?
Seriously.
It means you chose this. Our film.
No, stop.
Stop. I don't want it anymore.
You should do this.
Hey, hey.
No!
I don't want it!
Eat it.
I don't want it anymore.
Come on!
I knew you'd be here.
My dad called. He is furious.
You didn't show up for your meeting.
Yeah, I'll explain it to Dad and Uncle Ramon.
Hi.
Are you Sir Liam's friend, too?
I'm Sep. I'm his friend from the orphanage.
I'm Via.
I'm Liam's girlfriend.
Come on, let's eat.
I'm okay.
What's the update about the delivery
of the explosives?
They said it's almost here.
I'll wait for it.
The Director might need you.
- They've started rolling already.
- Okay, Sir Liam.
- Who are you?
- Don't run.
- Don't move!
Liam!
Who are you?
Uncle Ramon.
What's the meaning of this?
Looks like you already made a decision.
Now, it's my turn to decide.
You're scared of the bullet,
but you're not scared of messing with me.
What happened to our agreement that
you'd be returning to Casa Fuerte?
I can't.
I can't just do everything you say.
You're making me do bad things for money!
We only need two tires.
Two tires and a can of kerosene.
Your mother will mourn over your ashes.
I love being on top.
It feels different when you have the power.
What a waste.
Better luck next time.
Dad, stop!
What are you doing here?
Via.
Passengers getting off at Husena...
this is your stop.
Get off. Hurry up.
Is there anyone else?
I can't let you do this.
I love him, Dad.
Time to get off.
This is the last stop.
Has everyone already gotten off?
Bad day?
I don't believe Friday the 13th is bad luck.
But I think it might be true today.
I escaped the hustle and bustle of the city
so I can at least breathe...
So I can unwind.
Wow!
The view is breathtaking.
This is the kind of view that goes unnoticed
during our trips.
Unseen scenery.
How would you know...
if there's another chance?
That even for once...
you'll get noticed?
What are you talking about?
I can clearly see you, because of that.
What?
I can see you clearly
because of your red shoes.
It's so bloody red.
And the heels are too high.
How can I not notice you?
You can't move forward
if all the weight is on your shoes.
Look at this.
Look.
See? It feels so light.
Right?
Go on, Miss. Try it.
Try to take your red shoes off.
You'll feel lighter, too.
Promise.
Go on.
Try it.
See?
The other one too.
How do you feel?
Am I right?
I told you it feels good to go barefoot.
Right?
It feels good to be barefoot.
And what you'll do next is you'll shout.
You're able to breathe now.
Right? You'll shout...
"It feels so good to breathe!"
Try it, go!
Go!
It feels good to breathe!
Louder!
More!
It feels good to breathe!
There you go! More!
See?
Dear...
Don't tell me...
you choose him over your own father?
I'm your father.
Don't you love me anymore?
You're pointing a gun at me.
I do, Dad.
I love you.
But Liam is all I have.
You have me.
I've always been there for you.
But...
ever since Mama died...
it was never the same.
With you...
With me.
You have to understand, Dad.
I love Liam.
I love him more than my own life.
Don't say that.
Come here, my child.
Give your dad a hug.
Dad.
- Via!
- Spoiled brat!
Via!
What do you know about love?
Dad, please, no! Don't, don't, please!
No, not Liam, please.
Please, not Liam.
Please, Dad.
Don't! Stop it!
Stop!
Stop, please.
That man is already worthless.
That's the problem with you!
Everyone should be useful to you!
Is it not enough that Liam is my boyfriend?
I love him!
Get out of here!
Stop it! Stop!
Love, love...
Dad, do you think we're different?
You're acting like that...
You think about nothing but power and money
because you lost Mom.
Don't you drag your mom into this.
Am I wrong?
Ever since Mom died,
I have lost you, too, Dad.
I was all alone.
I've never felt so alone in my whole life.
I used to always think...
that I should have gone with Mom.
That only changed because of Liam.
Because of Liam.
I hold on to my life
because of what he made me feel.
So if you want to take him away from me, go!
Go ahead.
Kill me first.
Dad! Dad, stop!
From now on,
you are no longer connected
to any of my businesses.
You won't have a say in
any of our transactions.
If you give me problems,
I will hurt not you,
but the people who matter to you.
That's enough, Dad. Stop.
Just go.
- Go, go.
- Remember this.
You'll regret staying alive.
Love.
Love, love...
Via.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, love.
I'm sorry...
You're really strong.
And cut!
- Cut!
- Yeah, hit him!
It's already cut!
He doesn't run out of...
It's already cut.
That's enough.
He has lots of energy.
I think you have to go home.
I want to be an action star.
Action star.
That's enough. It's already late.
I think you need to go home.
You're already sleepy.
Where's Sir Liam?
He can instruct the service vehicle
to bring you home.
- Borj, where's...
- Boss Bro?
Miss Joyce, I was with Sir Liam earlier
while waiting for the props.
But when I returned to greet the suppliers,
Sir Liam wasn't there anymore.
Maybe VLH called him over to Blacksmith.
How about this?
Did you see VLH's face when he saw my boss?
He was fuming mad like a dragon.
That's true.
I almost called the firefighters
because I thought he would spit fire.
Excuse me, Madam Megan...
But it is such a waste how your boss
is good-looking but grumpy.
Silly.
Sep, dear. Do you want me to
bring you back to the orphanage?
Miss Joyce,
I still want to watch the filming.
One more take.
Do you still want to watch our filming?
One last take, okay?
Promise? And then you'll go home.
Okay, one more.
- One more. One more.
- Alright, one more.
Give some punches.
- Go, Sep!
- Go!
- Energy!
- He has lots of energy...
- Superman.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
He's not acting anymore!
- Sep!
- Call a medic!
- Sep, what's wrong?
- Sep...
Sep.
- Medic!
Here, here!
Via.
You shouldn't have intervened.
No. I meant everything I said.
I can't lose you, Liam.
But based on what I heard,
you know that your dad is mad at me...
because of our real business.
I lied.
I lied when I said...
I didn't know about my dad's business.
I know everything.
The illegal ones, too.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
What's important is that he let you go.
We can put that behind us now.
We can start over again.
Thank you...
Love.
Everything's okay now.
[5 Missed Calls]
[8 Messages]
[Sep collapsed at the set.]
It's Sep.
Wait, wait.
- I can do it.
- Be careful.
Wait. Wait.
Don't force it, please.
- Don't force it.
- I can do it.
Wait.
Slowly.
Joyce.
Liam, what happened to you?
This is nothing. I'm okay.
Are you okay? You don't look okay.
Where's Sep?
He's okay, Joyce.
How's his condition?
He's inside.
Sep.
Sister.
Sep, how are you? How are you feeling?
Sir Liam, I'm okay.
Looks like you're the one
who should go to the hospital.
Is that real or just makeup?
This is just makeup. Don't worry about me.
I'm okay.
You should regain your strength.
What happened to you?
I'm sorry. If I knew you were together,
I wouldn't bother Liam.
It's fine.
Liam loves the kid.
I know he'll beat himself up
if something bad happens to Sep.
- Sir Liam.
- Yes?
Can you be an action star
even if you have a weak heart?
Sep has a heart disease.
He got it from his father.
The doctor has seen him already.
He said Sep needed to rest.
He already took his medicines.
Sister.
I'm sorry, Sister.
I'm sorry Sep got tired in our set.
If I only knew...
No one wanted this to happen, dear.
Don't worry.
I'm okay. I can still do TikTok.
Is that TikTok?
What kind of move is that? Ouch.
You're heavy.
Are you okay?
How about me?
I know the best cardiologist in Manila.
I can give him a call. So we can be sure.
Yes, please...
Love.
I'll call him.
That's deep.
Joyce.
Don't get mad at me.
This time...
It is not my choice anymore.
What do you mean?
I was gone earlier...
because I received news...
that I was kicked out from
the Herrera Group of Companies.
That means...
I'm no longer part of Blacksmith.
I can't go back to Casa Fuerte either.
Is that how mad your father is?
That you chose the film over Casa Fuerte?
I went against a major investor.
What will happen to our movie?
You're no longer part of our project?
You're done after the first filming?
I have no choice but to start over again.
Why don't we make our own film?
What?
What about your film with Josh at Blacksmith?
Liam...
You're the reason I accepted that project.
Because of your talent, vision,
and dedication.
You.
I know about the deal you made
with your father and Congressman Ramon.
Josh told me about it.
Maybe that project isn't really for me.
Maybe we are just forcing it.
Joyce... I don't want you to be impulsive.
I'm not being impulsive.
I'm telling you right now
that I want us to make a movie.
Make sure you'll give me creative freedom.
And on one condition.
Part of what we'll make from the movie
will go to this orphanage.
I've already fallen in love
with the kids here.
Especially with Sep.
He has become important to me.
Joyce, I won't say no to that.
Deal?
Deal.
My friend.
Why did you suddenly want to see me?
What is this?
Open it.
What's this for, Congressman?
That's money collected from
my cockpit arenas in the province.
Use that money for the new subdivisions
that Casa Fuerte is developing.
And from now on...
you'll take the jobs Liam used to do.
Why? What did you do to my son?
Don't worry.
Your son is alive.
You have to thank my daughter.
Because if not for Via,
it would have been Liam's head
in that bag instead of money.
And you'll have to do the next collection.
What can you do?
Your favorite son abandoned you.
Here are the copies
of our sequence breakdown.
One for you...
One for you.
Give that to me.
The one you're holding. Let me have it.
Give me that.
Josh, let me have that.
New direction.
I saw the scenes you already shot.
I didn't like it.
It's so disappointing!
I want our hero to be very manly.
He must have swag.
Guys, imagine this...
Our hero is running with a leather jacket on.
He's holding the hand of his leading lady,
a sexy woman.
This is an action scene.
But, of course,
our hero is good at fight scenes.
He will protect his helpless leading lady.
Help!
And then, he will defeat all the enemies.
And they slowly kiss.
No!
That's what I want to see.
That's the kind of film
that will make him win the elections.
VLH, maybe it's better
if the leading lady can fight.
Imagine a fight scene like this.
The hero and his leading lady
are both fighting.
Let's show
that the woman knows how to use nunchuck...
That she can also fight.
There's no difference
between a man and a woman.
When it comes to fighting,
all you need is heart and skills.
Wait, VLH.
What happened to the original story?
We insisted on having an empowered heroine
in the movie, right?
And it goes well with my political platform
as vice mayor.
Women's rights,
as well as the rights of the LGBT community.
Vice mayor?
I thought you'd run for Congress?
Uncle Ramon told me to run as vice mayor
of my hometown for now,
because it will be a sure win.
It's up to you what position you want.
But we shouldn't narrow down
the demographic your film can reach.
Josh, your male voters will get turned off.
To make the hero stronger,
the woman should be weak.
Well...
I guess I'm right.
I think this film is not for me anymore.
Sorry.
I don't want to hurt anyone,
but I've already made a decision.
I won't do this film anymore.
I will buy out my contract.
If you have any questions,
you can talk to my lawyer.
Actually, I can recommend
a leading lady who will be eager
to accept this project...
Especially the story you want, VLH.
Again, I... I'm sorry.
And thanks to all of you.
And Josh...
Good luck.
Is Maxine busy right now?
Aunt Tess, this is Hans, my friend.
You look good together.
Liam, your family owns Casa Fuerte, right?
- Yes.
- An accident happened
at your construction site.
They want me to handle the case.
Did someone die in Casa Fuerte?
I'm surrounded by stupid people!
Spare me, Ramon.
I'm just new here.
That's why I need veterans.
This is Lando, my most trusted gunman.
You'll see his face last
if you fail again, Danilo.
Why did you have to get
the black sheep of the Herreras
for a boyfriend?
You could have gotten Vergil instead.
Mom, are you still concerned about money?
This is not about money.
This is about your career.
I have my own mind.
You stepped on me.
That's why you're not on the ground.
I'll let you indulge in your craziness.
But the next time you sign a contract,
you will do it even if it comes from a demon.
It's not too late.
We can still break away
from Congressman Ramon.
I know I wasn't the best father
to you and your sibling.